Hello, hello friends, today we will talk
about this plan for the Max plan that has already been discussed above. Friends, today I will
tell you how this plan works,
what features it has, and there are many
pattern plans. So before we talk about that, do not
forget to subscribe to the school. You
can subscribe
because it is
very important. So now let's talk
first. There are two types of admissions,
individual and world famous.
In the footer, the association needs two or three children. This
shoulder is available. Let's talk about entry.
Entry is from 18 years
and subscribe.
And
this year's child can be admitted.
And the expense of 180 days, which is for the post, can be
talked about. Like, don't tell me, if there is
gas, how are all your expenses from there? If
I am admitted in a minute, then
you are in the hospital. The expense of getting out of the hospital can
come for a day. When is it in between for which you are
bringing medicine from the medical shop? In this section, the
alarm has everything.  Tell me
now let's talk about Vishwa Benefit in which
reply left hand free fruit benefit
means the nutrition of 10 lakhs for those who have it, the
welfare of your Amla,
your eighth heart, your house, your treatment
done for which there is a pending amount of 2 lakhs, if you have
not subscribed to this channel for that then
please
subscribe
because you
can take it like this, you can
take Bigg Boss MB card from inside even in Sandy Bar, so
think how many times and then you can take it once,
three times, four, five or six times as many times as you
want, now there is no claim
bonus, there is no claim bonus, like if we have
taken a policy today, I am not
taking chocolate or you are not taking this product in the past, then if
you permit its care renewal for the next year, then
fifty percent no claim bonus can be added on it,
means you have a policy of 10 lakhs, it is a thing of 15 lakhs
every second year, what will happen in the second year so
that you do not take any problem in the second year,
then it is done for the third year
because if I do not practice then  Just
because it is worth 20 lakhs, you get the benefit of petrol in two years,
what is the list of health benefits, like step wise, like
you take medical treatment, brother, you do
that or you break it or you roam around,
whatever, you get this point
in your hand, so as you look, you get it on the
left side from
2014, now you can see, the
individual single member has
percentage points and how much percentage in walnut
and the capacity is from 2251 to 3000,
so Prashant Palace of voters is 201, they
clean them, so it has this facility, if
you want this application for
you, then let's
talk about it, you
can check,
like if someone does it for ₹5,
then do
not forget to subscribe to it,
how many members are there in the Loot Sirwali family,
dial four numbers at home
and the tower which should be transferred
for checkup of health or like I am telling you the
troubled post also, you can get treatment  I am impressed by the ad, if there is
news of the Sangh, then you can get this mask done for Meghnad also, whether you
share it with him or if you are
sharing it in some form, then till that time the
hatred is
subscribed in it and
according to the above up to one crore,
thousands of people read in the Pushpi that is going on, let's
talk about Arora Glass
₹2000 ₹2000 for a glance cashless, you understand, that is, as much as
you can take in this episode
and when it comes to replacement,
you get up to the first rupee
that our treatment for kidneys can be a
spoon of papaya
and festivals, like first come, it does
not work at all, first you can get
your treatment done at home in that, you can get
Clash Of
Yours done, you can get your treatment done at home, so in that,
like
you
can subscribe to [music], so in this, this
subscription is
also
kind of
what happens in government job school, the question is
translated in the body of the year,
not to hurt anyone, the initiative that has been taken is
with me, that should be done
transparently and will keep
taking it for Meghnad and  If
you subscribe to Ghar, then
you will get the
best doctor for you, get it done,
one more option in benefits is of
hospital cash for friends, in this way you
can take it, like if someone takes a post from 1.3 lakh to 5
lakh, then you get ₹2000 for the
chance of reading, and if someone asks for 67 lakh to
15 minutes, then it is ₹2000, and if someone subscribes
from 20 lakh to 1000, then within
24 hours he is admitted
in the hospital,
subscribe to the maximum,
as I will tell you, if you
subscribe, then
you will get the subscribe
percentage news, if you give it, then
175 percent is less in the hands and legs, the union has decided, then you will
get this side, in
which you have
subscribed
and subscribe,
like and subscribe, subscribe, subscribe, subscribe, subscribe,
subscribe, subscribe,
that there will be a majority in this, now listen and the
decision will increase, this is the best last, let's
talk about it, secondly, no claim bonus
Claim Bonus Mala up to 50,000 Maya
Pata for a year Bye-bye and there will be
no effect on the claim bonus, so if the
claim comes from the clear side, then like you, Mala Bainsla's
pole has been made, it is a super soft combo, which
means that you will be left with 68 items, there are
checkered ones like the fool is applying it
and many other things are covered in the middle,
now let's talk about the crotch, after this cream, there is a
little balance of elements, which goes where
two matches, which
Raghbir like Delhi,
Mumbai, Navi Mumbai, Kolkata, home,
so friends, this subscription has been told to you,
you explain it, now if you have any questions, you
can ask me, you can type your total in the comment box, I will
definitely answer you
about you.